

Centretek 8318 Forrest St. Ellicott City MD 21043 July 31, 2019

Dear Ryan,

I am writing to express interest the Front End Developer position at Centretek.

During my 19 years experience as a Web Designer and Front End Developer at Fastspot, R2integrated, DuClaw Brewing Company, North Charles Street Design Organization and the University of Maryland Baltimore County, I have honed my skills in web development using Wordpress, CSS/SASS, HTML, and JQuery. I have collaborated with art directors to deliver fully-functioning web sites within strict deadlines.

I am exited by the opportunity to bring my skills to one of the top web development agencies in Baltimore. Centretek offers a team-oriented environment, with plenty of room for growth and leadership potential, which also appeals to me.

Please visit www.aaronweidele.com to see examples of my work. If I may answer any additional questions for you, please do not hesitate to contact me at 443.207.1468 or at aweidele@gmail.com. Thank you for your time and consideration, and I look forward to speaking with you soon.

Sincerely,

Aaron Weidele





SKILLS

Responsive web design

HTML,CSS/SASS/LESS

PHP

Javascript/JQuery

Drupal 8

Wordpress

Sitecore

Gulp

Git

SourceTree

Jira

Shopify

MailChimp + MailChimp API

MySQL

PayPal/Payflow

Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere, After Effects, Flash)

UX Design

Usability Testing

Motion Graphics

Experience with Google Analytics

EDUCATION

1995-2000

University of Maryland Baltimore County / B.A. Imaging and Digital Arts

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016–2017, 2017–Present Front-End Developer, R2integrated

Collaborated with designers, back-end developers, and QA to build websites and components in Drupal 8 and Sitecore

Built component library for future Drupal 8 and Sitecore projects to facilitate faster development

Acquia Certified Front End Specialist - D8

2017–2018 Web Developer, Fastspot

Collaborated with the design and UX teams to build websites for higher ed and museums, using Wordpress and Bigtree

2014–2016 Front-End Developer, DuClaw Brewing Company

Worked with designers to develop microsites for festivals and special beer releases

Developed distributor order forms using PHP and MySQL

Migrated web store to Shopify, and set up Shopify POS for merchandise sales at festivals

2010–2014 Interactive Designer, North Charles Street Design Organization

Design and development of interactive recruitment campaigns for higher education. Campaigns included an email series and landing site.

Build custom Wordpress themes for advancement campaign websites.

Motion graphics for digital signs

Awards:

Gold Award / New Media / Higher Education Marketing Report's 27th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

Silver Award / Website / Higher Education Marketing Report's 26th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

Silver Award / Video Viewbook / Higher Education Marketing Report's 26th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

1999–2010 New Media Specialist, University of Maryland Baltimore County





REFERENCES

Jodi Swartz

Email: jodimswartz@gmail.com

Phone: 443.804.5954

Jessica Wyman

Email: hello@wymanprojects.com

Phone: 646.238.9024